const qBank = [
    {
        question: "What is the 2nd longest river in Africa?",
        answers: ["Nile", "Congo", "Niger", "White Nile"],
        correct: "Congo",
        questionId: "000001",
    },
    {
        question: "What year did Paul Kagame become president of Rwanda?",
        answers: ["1994", "1996", "2000", "2003"],
        correct: "2000",
        questionId: "000002",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these is not a capital city?",
        answers: ["Rabat, Morocco", "Windhoek, Namibia", "Abidjan, Ivory Coast", "Abuja, Nigeria"],
        correct: "Abidjan, Ivory Coast",
        questionId: "000003",
    },
    {
        question: "What was the previous name of the African Union?",
        answers: ["Organization of African States", "Organization of African Unity", "Organization of African Nations", "Organization of African Union"],
        correct: "Organization of African Unity",
        questionId: "000004",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country has won the most African Cup of Nations?",
        answers: ["Ghana","Cameroon", "Egypt", "Nigeria"],
        correct: "Egypt",
        questionId: "000005",
    },
    {
        question: "Ali’s Rumble in the Jungle was fought in which city?",
        answers: ["Kinshasa, Congo DR", "Yaoude, Cameroun", "Nairobi, Kenya", "Kampala, Uganda"],
        correct: "Kinshasa, Congo DR",
        questionId: "000006",
    },
    {
        question: "What’s the title of Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie’s 1st publication?",
        answers: ["Half of a Yellow Sun", "Purple Hibiscus", "Americanah", "We Should All Be Feminists"],
        correct: "Purple Hibiscus",
        questionId: "000007",
    },
    {
        question: "“A Dance of the Forests” is an acclaimed theatre piece by?",
        answers: ["Efua Sutherland", "Wole Soyinka", "J.P. Clark", "Bole Butake"],
        correct: "Wole Soyinka",
        questionId: "000008",
    },
    {
        question: "The 1st African actor to win an Oscar was?",
        answers: ["Lupita Nyong’o", "Omar Sharif", "Barkhad Abdi", "Charlize Theron"],
        correct: "Charlize Theron",
        questionId: "000009",
    },
    {
        question: "What genre of music was Papa Wemba known for?",
        answers: ["Congolese Rumba","Senegalese Mbalax", "Afrobeat", "South African House"],
        correct: "Congolese Rumba",
        questionId: "000010",
    },
    {
        question: "When was the Mali Empire founded?",
        answers: ["1235", "1100", "1605", "1452"],
        correct: "1235",
        questionId: "000011",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country has an AK-47 on their flag?",
        answers: ["Congo DR", "Somalia", "Mozambique", "Zimbabwe"],
        correct: "Mozambique",
        questionId: "000012",
    },
    {
        question: "Which former president was known as Mwalimu? Swahili for teacher.",
        answers: ["Julius Nyerere", "Jomo Kenyatta", "Kenneth Kaunda", "Samora Machel"],
        correct: "Julius Nyerere ",
        questionId: "000013",
    },
    {
        question: "Bob Marley played a concert at who’s independence?",
        answers: ["Senegal", "Ghana", "South Africa", "Zimbabwe"],
        correct: "Zimbabwe",
        questionId: "000014",
    },
    {
        question: "Kunta Kinte was from which modern-day country?",
        answers: ["Senegal", "Nigeria", "The Gambia", "Ghana"],
        correct: "The Gambia",
        questionId: "000015",
    },
    {
        question: "The Biafran war was a civil war in which country?",
        answers: ["Congo DR", "Sudan", "Nigeria", "Liberia"],
        correct: "Nigeria",
        questionId: "000016",
    },
    {
        question: "When was the Sokoto Caliphate started?",
        answers: ["1804", "1851", "1832", "1816"],
        correct: "1804",
        questionId: "000017",
    },
    {
        question: "What year was Ellen Johnson Sirleaf 1st elected president?",
        answers: ["2000", "2006", "2018", "2012"],
        correct: "2006",
        questionId: "000018",
    },
    {
        question: "Ahmed Sekou Toure was the former president of:",
        answers: ["Mali", "Senegal", "Ivory Coast", "Guinea"],
        correct: "Guinea",
        questionId: "000019",
    },
    {
        question: "How many island nations are in Africa?",
        answers: ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
        correct: "6",
        questionId: "000020",
    },
    {
        question: "Which modern day nations made up the Ghana Empire?",
        answers: ["Ghana, Togo, Ivory Coast", "Mauritania, Senegal, Mali", "Mali, Ghana, Burkina Faso", "Nigeria, Niger, Benin"],
        correct: "Mauritania, Senegal, Mali",
        questionId: "000021",
    },
    {
        question: "The great Carthaginian Empire started in which modern day country?",
        answers: ["Ethiopia", "Egypt", "Sudan", "Tunisia"],
        correct: "Tunisia",
        questionId: "000022",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the capital of Chad?",
        answers: ["Niamey", "Bujumbura", "Juba", "N’Djamena"],
        correct: "N’Djamena",
        questionId: "000023",
    },
    {
        question: "Where is the ECOWAS headquartered?",
        answers: ["Dakar", "Abuja", "Bamako", "Accra"],
        correct: "Abuja",
        questionId: "000024",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the largest lake in Africa by area?",
        answers: ["Turkana", "Nyassa", "Tanganyika", "Victoria"],
        correct: "Victoria",
        questionId: "000025",
    },
    {
        question: "Where are the Nubian Pyramids located?",
        answers: ["Egypt", "Sudan", "Ethiopia", "Chad"],
        correct: "Sudan",
        questionId: "000026",
    },
    {
        question: "Gaborone is the capital of:",
        answers: ["Malawi", "Botswana", "Zambia", "Burundi"],
        correct: "Botswana",
        questionId: "000027",
    },
    {
        question: "The Niger river starts in which country?",
        answers: ["Mali", "Niger", "Guinea", "Senegal"],
        correct: "Guinea",
        questionId: "000028",
    },
    {
        question: "Where is the EAC headquartered? EAC = East African Community.",
        answers: ["Nairobi, Kenya", "Arusha, Tanzania", "Kigali, Rwanda", "Entebbe, Uganda"],
        correct: "Arusha, Tanzania",
        questionId: "000029",
    },
    {
        question: "Port Louis is the capital of:",
        answers: ["Mozambique", "Equatorial Guinea", "Mauritius", "Cape Verde"],
        correct: "Mauritius",
        questionId: "000030",
    },
    {
        question: "Bujumbura is the capital of:",
        answers: ["The Gambia", "Burundi", "Comoros", "Guinea Bissau"],
        correct: "Burundi",
        questionId: "000031",
    },
    {
        question: "Porto-Novo is the capital of:",
        answers: ["Cape Verde", "Benin", "Mauritius", "Guinea Bissau"],
        correct: "Benin",
        questionId: "000032",
    },
    {
        question: "The Kingdom of Benin is in which modern country?",
        answers: ["Central African Republic", "Nigeria", "Ghana", "Cameroon"],
        correct: "Nigeria",
        questionId: "000033",
    },
    {
        question: "The Serengeti is located in which country?",
        answers: ["Zambia", "Zimbabwe", "Kenya", "Tanzania"],
        correct: "Tanzania",
        questionId: "000034",
    },
    {
        question: "The Great Mosque of Djenne is located in:",
        answers: ["Niger", "Sudan", "Nigeria", "Mali"],
        correct: "Mali",
        questionId: "000035",
    },
    {
        question: "Lalibela, home to the famous rock-hewn churches is in:",
        answers: ["Kenya", "Zimababwe", "Ethiopia", "Congo DR"],
        correct: "Ethiopia",
        questionId: "000036",
    },
    {
        question: "Where is the African Renaissance Monument is pointing to?",
        answers: ["Martin Luther King Memorial, USA", "Eiffel Tower, France", "Statue of Liberty, USA", "Christ the Redeemer, Brazil"],
        correct: "Statue of Liberty, USA",
        questionId: "000037",
    },
    {
        question: "Which is not a South Africa national team nickname?",
        answers: ["Bafana Bafana", "Springboks", "Proteas", "Blue cranes"],
        correct: "Blue cranes",
        questionId: "000038",
    },
    {
        question: "Which team has the most World Cup appearances?",
        answers: ["Cameroon", "Senegal", "Ghana", "Nigeria"],
        correct: "Cameroon",
        questionId: "000039",
    },
    {
        question: "Who’s the first man to record a marathon run under 2 hours?",
        answers: ["Wilson Kipsang", "Eliud Kipchoge", "Haile Gebrselassie", "Dennis Kemetto"],
        correct: "Eliud Kipchoge",
        questionId: "000040",
    },
    {
        question: "Dikembe Mutombo is a former NBA player from:",
        answers: ["Congo DR", "Cameroon", "Nigeria", "Senegal"],
        correct: "Congo DR",
        questionId: "000041",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country’s president was a former international football star?",
        answers: ["South Africa", "Liberia", "Ghana", "Tunisia"],
        correct: "Liberia",
        questionId: "000042",
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the first team to win gold for football at the Olympics:?",
        answers: ["Nigeria", "Ghana", "Cameroon", "Morocco"],
        correct: "Nigeria",
        questionId: "000043",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country has not won Gold for Olympics boxing?",
        answers: ["Algeria", "Kenya", "South Africa", "Nigeria"],
        correct: "Nigeria",
        questionId: "000044",
    },
    {
        question: "Who’s the only African to win FIFA Player of the Year?",
        answers: ["Didier Dogba", "George Weah", "Samuel Eto", "Mo Salah"],
        correct: "George Weah",
        questionId: "000045",
    },
    {
        question: "Maria Mutola is an Olympic 800m champion from:",
        answers: ["South Africa", "Angola", "Mozambique", "Zimbabwe"],
        correct: "Mozambique",
        questionId: "000046",
    },
    {
        question: "Who authored the Booker Prize winner “The Famished Road”?",
        answers: ["Wole Sonyinka", "Ngugi wa Thiong’o", "Chinua Achebe", "Ben Okri"],
        correct: "Ben Okri",
        questionId: "000047",
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the main character in Things Fall Apart?",
        answers: ["Enzima", "Okonkwo", "Nwoye", "Mr. Brown"],
        correct: "Okonkwo",
        questionId: "000048",
    },
    {
        question: "Ngugi wa Thiong’o is an award winning author from:",
        answers: ["Tanzania", "Kenya", "Nigeria", "Ghana"],
        correct: "Kenya",
        questionId: "000049",
    },
    {
        question: "Who wrote the “Burger’s Daughter”?",
        answers: ["Nadine Gordimer", "Aminatta Forna", "Mariama Ba", "Ayi Kwei Armah"],
        correct: "Nadine Gordimer",
        questionId: "000050",
    },
    {
        question: "Dubbed Africa’s greatest feminist writer, Mariama Ba is from:",
        answers: ["Senegal", "Ivory Coast", "Mali", "Burkina Faso"],
        correct: "Senegal",
        questionId: "000051",
    },
    {
        question: "Nuruddin Farah’s novel “From a Crooked Rib” (1970) is about:",
        answers: ["Corruption in the Somalian government", "Sufferings of women in Somalian society", "The division of the Somalian state", "The ethnic divide in Somalian society"],
        correct: "Sufferings of women in Somalian society",
        questionId: "000052",
    },
    {
        question: "Disgrace is a Booker award winner from which writer?",
        answers: ["Ben Okri", "J M Coetzee", "Bernandine Everisto", "Nadine Gordimer"],
        correct: "J M Coetzee",
        questionId: "000053",
    },
    {
        question: "What is Youssou N'dour’s nationality?",
        answers: ["Senegalese", "Malian", "Guinean", "Burkinabe"],
        correct: "Senegalese",
        questionId: "000054",
    },
    {
        question: "Cheb Khaled who sang the original Aicha is from:",
        answers: ["Morocco", "Algeria", "Egypt", "Tunisia"],
        correct: "Algeria",
        questionId: "000055",
    },
    {
        question: "Fela Kuti is known for which musical genre?",
        answers: ["Kizomba", "Coupe-Decale", "Afrobeat", "Kwaito"],
        correct: "Afrobeat",
        questionId: "000056",
    },
    {
        question: "Where did the musical genre Highlife originate?",
        answers: ["Nigeria", "Kenya", "Congo DR", "Ghana"],
        correct: "Ghana",
        questionId: "000057",
    },
    {
        question: "Who is considered the King of Rumba?",
        answers: ["Papa Wemba", "Franco Luambo", "Kanda Bongo Man", "Madilu System"],
        correct: "Franco Luambo",
        questionId: "000058",
    },
    {
        question: "Amapiano is a musical genre from:",
        answers: ["Kenya", "Congo DR", "Uganda", "South Africa"],
        correct: "South Africa",
        questionId: "000059",
    },
    {
        question: "Netflix hit series Queen Sono was produced in:",
        answers: ["Nigeria", "South Africa", "Kenya", "Morocco"],
        correct: "South Africa",
        questionId: "000060",
    },
    {
        question: "Which artist has not won a Grammy?",
        answers: ["Angelique Kidjo", "Fela Kuti", "Youssou N’Dour", "Mariam Makeba"],
        correct: "Fela Kuti",
        questionId: "000061",
    },
    {
        question: "Which artisit has not won a Grammy?",
        answers: ["Richard Bona", "Soweto Gospel Choir", "Ali Farka Toure", "Salif Keita"],
        correct: "Salif Keita",
        questionId: "000062",
    },
    {
        question: "Lucky Dube was from which country? His country’s biggest selling reggae artist.",
        answers: ["Kenya", "Ghana", "South Africa", "Senegal"],
        correct: "South Africa",
        questionId: "000063",
    },
    {
        question: "Brenda Fassie is famous Afropop singer from:",
        answers: ["South Africa", "Zimbabwe", "Botswana", "Zambia"],
        correct: "South Africa",
        questionId: "000064",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these is not in the world’s top 20 list of uranium producers?",
        answers: ["Niger", "Congo DR", "Namibia", "South Africa"],
        correct: "Congo DR",
        questionId: "000065",
    },
    {
        question: "Who’s the world’s #1 producer of cacao?",
        answers: ["Cameroon", "Nigeria", "Ghana", "Ivory Coast"],
        correct: "Ivory Coast",
        questionId: "000066",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these companies is the most valuable in 2020?",
        answers: ["Nasper, SA", "Dangote Cement, NG", "Safaricon, KE", "Maroc Telcom, MA"],
        correct: "Nasper, SA",
        questionId: "000067",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these companies is the most valuable in 2020?",
        answers: ["Dangote Cement, NG", "Safaricon, KE", "Maroc Telcom, MA", "MTN Group, SA"],
        correct: "Maroc Telcom, MA",
        questionId: "000068",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these countries produces the most diamonds? Produced 18M carats in 2019.",
        answers: ["South Africa", "Congo DR", "Botswana", "Angola"],
        correct: "Botswana",
        questionId: "000069",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country had the most tech startup investment in 2019? It brought in $149 million total funding.",
        answers: ["South Africa", "Nigeria", "Kenya", "Egypt"],
        correct: "Kenya",
        questionId: "000070",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country had the most tech companies receive $1M+ funding in 2019? Total raised by 98 African companies was $1.25B.",
        answers: ["Kenya", "Nigeria", "Egyot", "South Africa"],
        correct: "South Africa",
        questionId: "000071",
    },
    {
        question: "Firstrand, the highest ranking African finance company is in:",
        answers: ["Nigeria", "South Africa", "Ghana", "Egypt"],
        correct: "",
        questionId: "000072",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these in not a Nobel Laureate?",
        answers: ["Wangari Maathai", "Kofi Annan", "Kwame Nkrumah", "Abiy Ahmed"],
        correct: "Kwame Nkrumah",
        questionId: "000073",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these is not a name of an Africa University?",
        answers: ["Makerere", "Dakar", "Cape Town", "Ibadan"],
        correct: "Dakar",
        questionId: "000074",
    },
    {
        question: "Finnish this title, “Ibrahim Prize for Achievement in African …”",
        answers: ["Business", "Innovation", "Leadership", "Activism"],
        correct: "Leadership",
        questionId: "000075",
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the current president of the African Development Bank?",
        answers: ["Donald Kaberuka", "Akinwumi Adesina", "Babacar N’diaye", "Omar Kabbaj"],
        correct: "Akinwumi Adesina",
        questionId: "000076",
    },
    {
        question: "Which ethnic group spoke of star Sirius B centuries before it was first pictured in 1970?",
        answers: ["Fulani", "Dogon", "Maasai", "Himba"],
        correct: "Dogon",
        questionId: "000077",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the meaning of Burkina Faso?",
        answers: ["Land of Independent People", "Land of Incorruptible People", "Land of Unconquerable People", "Land of Outstanding People"],
        correct: "Land of Incorruptible People",
        questionId: "000078",
    },
    {
        question: "Which past president co-created the philosophy of ‘Negritude’? The movement sought to assert and valorize distinct African characteristics, values and aesthetics.",
        answers: ["Thomas Sankara", "Sekou Toure", "Patrice Lumumba", "Leopold Senghor"],
        correct: "Leopold Senghor",
        questionId: "000079",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country’s president has a JSD from Yale University?",
        answers: ["Liberia", "Malawi", "South Africa", "Togo"],
        correct: "Malawi",
        questionId: "000080",
    }
]

export default (n = 5) => Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));